[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Charles never _________ breakfast in the morning.",
        "options": [
            "ate",
            "eat",
            "eats",
            "eaten"
        ],
        "answer": "eats"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The water for the pasta _________. Can you put the pasta in for me?",
        "options": [
            "boil",
            "is boiling",
            "boils",
            "is boils"
        ],
        "answer": "is boiling"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "John is very good at languages. _________ four languages very well.",
        "options": [
            "He speaks",
            "He speak",
            "He is speak",
            "He is speaking"
        ],
        "answer": "He speaks"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Christian _________ to work by car. He works from home.",
        "options": [
            "goes",
            "is going",
            "doesn't go",
            "isn't going"
        ],
        "answer": "doesn't go"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The Mississippi River _________ into the Gulf of Mexico.",
        "options": [
            "flow",
            "is flow",
            "flows",
            "is flowing"
        ],
        "answer": "flows"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Can we stop soon? _________ to feel really tired.",
        "options": [
            "I'm starting",
            "I start",
            "I'm start",
            "I starts"
        ],
        "answer": "I'm starting"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Natalie _________ at the moment for her drivers test on Friday.",
        "options": [
            "is study",
            "study",
            "studies",
            "is studying"
        ],
        "answer": "eats"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "My parents _________ in an apartment temporarily until their house is finished next week.",
        "options": [
            "live",
            "lives",
            "is living",
            "are living"
        ],
        "answer": "are living"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "_________ with you at Amazon?.",
        "options": [
            "Is he work",
            "Does he work",
            "Is he working",
            "Is he work"
        ],
        "answer": "Does he work"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "I have to go now. _________ late.",
        "options": [
            "It get",
            "It gets",
            "It's getting",
            "It's get"
        ],
        "answer": "It's getting"
    }
]